var baseball = [
	{
		front: "Padres",
		back: "San Diego"
	}, {
		front: "Angels",
		back: "Anaheim"
	}, {
		front: "Dodgers",
		back: "Los Angeles"
	},{
		front: "Giants",
		back: "San Francisco"
	}, {
		front: "Athletics",
		back: "Oakland"
	}, {
		front: "Mariners",
		back: "Seattle"
	}, {
		front: "Rockies",
		back: "Denver"
	}, {
		front: "Astros",
		back: "Houston"
	}, {
		front: "Diamondbacks",
		back: "Arizona"
	}, {
		front: "Red Sox",
		back: "Boston"
	}, {
		front: "Yankees",
		back: "New York"
	}, {
		front: "Marlins",
		back: "Miami"
	}, {
		front: "Nationals",
		back: "Washington"
	}
];

module.exports = baseball;